graphicsfactory.com 2010-06-02

# Graphics Factory.com - Privacy Policy

[](http://www.graphicsfactory.com/) | **Privacy Statement**  
Effective Date: August 23, 2006|   
---|---|---  

GraphicsFactory.com has been reviewed by the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user's trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the site http://www.graphicsfactory.com/ and http://www.graphicsfactory.com/. 

Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Robert Gillen at 1-800-339-2383 or [privacy@graphicsfactory.com](mailto:privacy@graphicsfactory.com). If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily address, you should contact [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

**Introduction**

Protecting your personal information is a core GraphicsFactory.com value. This privacy statement describes how GraphicsFactory.com collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: www.GraphicsFactory.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding GraphicsFactory.com's use of your personal information and the steps you can take to change it. 

We use visitors contact information (such as Email addresses) and financial information (credit card data, name, billing address). Contact information is only used to fill customer orders or to correspond regarding such orders. Financial information collected is only used to bill customers for voluntary purchases of products and services. 

We refuse to sell, trade or otherwise transfer any type of customer data - email addresses, mailing addresses, etc., - to other companies or individuals. 

**Use of Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

We use both session ID cookies and/or persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. 

We set a persistent cookie to store your username and password, so you don't have to enter it more than once. 

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as downloading clip art, will not be available. 

Some of our business partners (e.g., Webtrends) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by GraphicsFactory.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any business partners. 

**Service Providers**

We use other third parties PayPal and Verisign to provide payment services on our site. When you join GraphicsFactory.com, we will share Billing address and payment information as necessary for the third party to provide that service. 

These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. 

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We have strong security measures in place to protect from the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control. Our site uses secure order forms for our customers to make purchases in safe and private manner. All data submitted through our secure forms is protected the entire online route - from the customer's computer to ours - with powerful SSL encryption technology. To learn more about SSL, [follow this link](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Secure_Sockets_Layer). 

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at [feedback@graphicsfactory.com](mailto:feedback@graphicsfactory.com). 

**Testimonials** If you post a testimonial on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of this site, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit on this site. 

**Use Of Member Information Collected**

We only use your Email address to send Email when we update the site, usually monthly. We never sell or share your Email address with other companies. You also have the option to not receive newsletters, this can be change in the edit account area once you are signed in. 

You can opt-out of receiving the update newsletters, but we may send occasional critical newsletters if we have important information to share about the workings of your membership. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. 

**Correct/Update/Contact**

This site gives users the option of changing, modifying or deleting information previously provided. To do so, or if you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please feel free to contact us using the information below. 

[privacy@graphicsfactory.com](mailto:privacy@graphicsfactory.com).

GraphicsFactory.com  
2051 E Red Hills Pkwy #2  
Saint George, UT 84770 

1-800-339-2383 

**Disclosure Statement**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.
